(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T17:46:23.930799",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
袋に詰められたナッツのような世間では
In a world like nuts packed in a bag,
誰もがそれぞれに出会った誰かと寄り添い合っている
everyone is snuggling up to someone they met.
そこに紛れ込んだ僕らはピーナッツみたいに
We're mixed in there like peanuts,
木の実のふりしながら微笑み浮かべる
smiling while pretending to be tree nuts.
幸運のテンプレートの上
On the template of happiness,
文字通り絵に描いたうわべの裏
right behind the picturesque surface,
テーブルを囲み手を合わせるその時さえ ありのままでは居られないまま
even when we sit around the table and put our hands together, we can't be ourselves.
隠し事だらけ 継ぎ接ぎだらけの home you know
A home full of secrets and patches, you know?
噛み砕いてもなくならない
Even when chewed up, they don't disappear,
本音が歯に挟まったまま
with truth still stuck in our teeth.
不安だらけ 成り行き任せの life and I know
Our life is so insecure and drifting, and I know
仮初めの日常だけれど
every day is just a temporary routine, but
ここに僕が居て あなたが居る
I'm here and you're here.
この事実だけでもう胃がもたれていく
Just by this truth, my stomach feels heavy.
化けの皮剥がれた一粒のピーナッツみたいに
Like a single peanut whose disguise has peeled off,
世間から一瞬で弾かれてしまう
we get instantly rejected from society.
そんな時こそ 曲がりなりにも良かったら
That is when I want to be by your side,
そばに居させて
if you'll have me.
共に焼かれ 揺られ 踏まれても 割れない殻みたいになるから
Even if we get roasted, shaken, and stepped on, we'll become unbreakable nutshells.
生まれた場所が木の上か 地面の中か それだけの違い
Whether you were born above a tree or underground, that's the only difference.
許されないほどに ドライなこの世界を
May the rain equally moisturize
等しく雨が湿らせますように
this unacceptably dry world.
時には冷たくて 騒がしい窓の向こう you know
The other side of the window is sometimes cold and noisy, you know?
星の一つも見つからない
Not even a single star can be found,
雷に満ちた日があっても良い
and days filled with thunder are fine too.
ミスだらけ アドリブ任せの show but I know
A show full of mistakes and improvisations, but I know
所詮ひとときの日常だから
after all, this is a fleeting daily life,
腹の中ででも流して寝よう
so let's digest it in our stomachs and sleep.
隠し事だらけ 継ぎ接ぎだらけの home you know
A home full of secrets and patches, you know?
とっておきの珍味合えも 残さず全部味わいながら
Savoring every single rare delicacy without leaving a scrap,
普通なんてない 正解なんてない life and I know
there is no normal, no right answer in life, and I know
仮初めの日常だけれど
every day is just a temporary routine, but
ここに僕が居て あなたが居る
I'm here and you're here.
この事実だけでもう胃がもたれていく
Just by this truth, my stomach feels heavy.
この一掴みの奇跡を 噛み締めていく
I continue to cherish this handful of a miracle.
時には冷たくて 騒がしい窓の向こう you know
The other side of the window is sometimes cold and noisy, you know?
星の一つも見つからない 雷に満ちた日があっても良い
Not even a single star can be found, and days filled with thunder are fine too.
ミスだらけ アドリブ任せの show but I know
A show full of mistakes and improvisations, but I know
所詮ひとときの日常だから 腹の中ででも流して寝よう
after all, this is a fleeting daily life, so let's digest it in our stomachs and sleep.
隠し事だらけ 継ぎ接ぎだらけの home you know
A home full of secrets and patches, you know?
とっておきの珍味合えも 残さず全部味わいながら
Savoring every single rare delicacy without leaving a scrap,
普通なんてない 正解なんてない life and I know
there is no normal, no right answer in life, and I know
仮初めの日常だけれど
every day is just a temporary routine, but
ここに僕が居て あなたが居る
I'm here and you're here.
この事実だけでもう胃がもたれていく
Just by this truth, my stomach feels heavy.
この一掴みの奇跡を 噛み締めていく
I continue to cherish this handful of a miracle.
普通なんてない 正解なんてない life and I know
there is no normal, no right answer in life, and I know
仮初めの日常だけれど
every day is just a temporary routine, but
ここに僕が居て あなたが居る
I'm here and you're here.
この事実だけでもう胃がもたれていく
Just by this truth, my stomach feels heavy.
この一掴みの奇跡を 噛み締めていく
I continue to cherish this handful of a miracle.
このひとつの 神様の奇跡を 噛み締めていく
Savoring this single, divine miracle.
噛み締めていく
Savoring it...
大義名分に痺れ切らした
Tired of high-sounding excuses,
苦渋の闇 怒号の渦の中
in bitter darkness and a whirlpool of roars,
始まりに孤独はつきものさ
loneliness always accompanies beginnings.
四面楚歌でも壁を突き破れ
Even when surrounded on all sides, smash through the walls!
予想外 風向きかき回せ
Unexpectedly, stir up the wind direction!
加速していく マグマの鼓動確かめて進め
Check the accelerating magma's heartbeat and move forward!
にやっと笑いた 死神の呼ぶ声がする
With a grin, I hear the grim reaper calling,
Do you believe yourself?
僕は始まった 栄光のゴールを見たいのさ
I've begun, wanting to see the glorious goal!
Shiny sword my diamond 悲しみと願いの結晶体に
Shiny sword, my diamond, a crystallization of sorrow and wishes.
僕ら使命を誓う それぞれの光を目指していく
We pledge our mission, aiming for our respective lights.
何度だって立ち上がって 僕は今日まで来たんだ
I've stood up time and time again to get to today.
It's time 一個の祈りが革命の確証 さあ輝け
It's time. A single prayer is proof of revolution. Now, shine!
汗と涙・mistake 蜜の味？ ハイエナの唾液まみれの泥道
Sweat, tears, mistakes... taste of honey? A muddy road covered in hyena drool.
ガラス細工 巧妙に施した
A glass craft, cleverly made.
100カラット？ きらめきに
100 carats? In the sparkle
ときめくほど眩しい奇跡を 世界が待っている
the world is waiting for a dazzling miracle to take its breath away!
Your sparkling smile is so sweet stone, bright illusion
Your sparkling smile is so sweet, bright illusion
Oh ダイヤモンド Smile (shine)
Oh, Diamond Smile (shine)
Your ダイヤモンド Smile (dream)
Your Diamond Smile (dream)
1秒先はもっともっともっと輝く
Shining more and more with every passing second
愛しちゃって 愛しちゃって 愛しちゃって
Falling in love, falling in love, falling in love
いいじゃないか more
Isn't it fine? More
永遠に煌めき
Sparkle eternally
Your sparkling smile is so sweet stone, bright illusion
Your sparkling smile is so sweet, bright illusion
Wow 世界にひとつさ 特別なその smile
Wow, there is only one in the world, that special smile
今日のため息振り返った明日の君
Today's sigh looking back at tomorrow's you
また「私なんて」ってセリフ
Again, that phrase "someone like me"
君には似合わないよ
Doesn't suit you at all
ほら ワンカラットの瞳(eyes)
Look, eyes of one carat
覗き込めば 吸い込まれそうさ ぎゅっと
If you peek, you'll be sucked right in
繋いだ手を また握りしめた
Holding hands tightly once again
プラチナのジェットにのって
Riding on a platinum jet
気まぐれな奇跡に酔って
Intoxicated by a whimsical miracle
瞬きが終る頃
By the time blinking ends
僕だけの君でいてね
Be only my girl
Oh ダイヤモンド Smile (shine)
Oh, Diamond Smile (shine)
Your ダイヤモンド Smile (dream)
Your Diamond Smile (dream)
1秒先はもっともっともっと輝く
Shining more and more with every passing second
キライな自分 好きな自分
The self I hate, the self I like
素直に言えたら イイね
It's nice if I can say it honestly
そう 星屑 も(shine) とろける ほど(dream)
Yes, stardust melting to the point of dream
甘い 運命 感じ て
Feeling a sweet destiny
愛し ちまっ て 愛し ちまっ て 愛し ちまっ て
Fall in love, fall in love, fall in love
いい じゃ ない か more
Isn't it fine? More
永遠に 煌めき
Sparkle eternally
Your sparkling smile is so sweet stone, bright illusion
Your sparkling smile is so sweet, bright illusion
Wow 今 以上の 君が 確実に見えるよ
Wow, I can surely see a you beyond now
言葉 よりも 先に 涙 溢れ ちゃう 時は
When tears overflow before words do
三日月 の ソファ で 少し 星を 数えようよ
Let's count stars on a crescent moon sofa
今 この 瞬間 を 笑い 合える そんな 僕ら だから
Because we are the kind of people who can laugh together
きっと 変わらない もの が ある
Surely, there is something that never changes
Oh ダイヤモンド Smile (shine)
Oh, Diamond Smile (shine)
Your ダイヤモンド Smile (dream)
Your Diamond Smile (dream)
1秒先はもっともっともっと輝く
Shining more and more with every passing second
It's time, it's time, Artemis
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy," 'cause the truth is, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう 見えないところでバタ足するんです
The swans give flutter kicks where you can't see
本能に順従 忠実 翻弄も重々承知 前途洋々だし...
Instinctively obedient and loyal; my future's bright...
だからたまに休眠しちゃうんです
So sometimes, I take a break
この目でしっかり見定めて 行き先地図上マークして
Looking closely and marking my destination on the map
近道あればそれが王道 はしゃる翼もあるなら上等
If there's a shortcut, or wings to fly, that's best
ヤバ爪割れた グルーで補修した それだけでなんか達成感
Oh no, I broke a nail and fixed it with glue—what accomplishment!
大事なのは自分 可愛がること 自分を愛さないと 他人も愛せない
What's important is loving yourself; love yourself first
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy," 'cause the truth is, I'm crazy
能ある鷹はそう 見えないところにピック隠すんです
A capable hawk hides its pick where you can't see
想像に一生懸命 現実態絶体絶命 発展途中だし...
Daydreaming hard, reality is desperate, I'm still developing...
だから不意にピッチ外れちゃうんです
So unexpectedly, I go off-pitch
その目に映らないだけだって やる気はメーター振り切って
You can't see it, but my motivation is maxed out
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
Always dreaming with all my might, and sleeping as well
ヤリ ちょっと痩せた 調子づいて喰食った それだけでなんで? 敗北感
Lost weight, got carried away and ate—why do I feel defeated?
すかさずに見目標 下方修正して 柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
Quickly revise goals downward; be flexible and adapt to win
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy," 'cause the truth is, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう ここぞというとき美を魅せるんです
The peacocks show off their beauty when it counts
五臓六腑 満身邁進 願望は痩身 美人 誘惑多発だし...
With heart and soul, desiring to be slim and beautiful...
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
That's why our willpower easily shatters
ヤバ まさか赤点(Red Point)!? いや ギリクリア!
Uh oh, a failing grade?! No, barely passed!
それだけでなんと全能感 大事なのは自分 認めてくこと
With just that, I feel almighty; accept yourself
自分を許さないと 他人も許さない
If you don't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others
だって本当はcrazy 白鳥たちはそう 見えないところでバタ足するんです
But the truth is, I'm crazy; swans flutter kick where you can't see
本能に順従 忠実 翻弄も重々承知 前途洋々だし...
Instinctively obedient and loyal; my future's bright...
だからたまに休眠しちゃうんです
So sometimes, I take a break
その目に映らないだけだって やる気はメーター振り切って
You can't see it, but my motivation is maxed out
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
Always dreaming with all my might, and sleeping as well
いつでも全力で夢見たその分 全力で眠ってもうて
Always dreaming and sleeping with all my might
調子にのって 調子に乗っていって 調子にのって
Getting carried away and getting ahead of myself
すかさずにもくきょう たんほしゅうせいして
Quickly revise goals downward without hesitation
じゅなんにりんきおうへん しんぺい かかち
Flexible and adaptable, changing seven ways to win
Please don't say you are lazy
Guys! 止めんな 止めんな 続けろよ
Guys! Don't stop, don't stop, keep it going!
Guys! No problem 安心しろ
Guys! No problem, rest easy.
嘲笑う奴から消えてくから
Those who sneer will just fade away,
逆・境・歓・迎!
Welcome adversity!
Guys! 自分を絶対に疑うな
Guys! Never doubt yourself.
Guys! That’s right 重要事項
Guys! That's right, it's essential.
必ずお前の運命と出会う日が来る Right away
The day you meet your destiny will come right away.
同調圧力なんてクソ喰らえ
To hell with peer pressure!
Go away! 右向け左へ
Go away! Look right, look left!
自己犠牲なんてクソ喰らえ
To hell with self-sacrifice!
Go away! 自分を愛で愛で
Go away! Love yourself, love yourself!
Play with me!!!
譲れないモノ主張して Discussion! OUTSIDER RODEO
Assert what you won't compromise! Discussion! OUTSIDER RODEO
Play with me!!!
お前と僕の“ガチ”で 化学反応→誕生→最優秀賞★
With your and my "seriousness," chemical reaction -> birth -> best award!
辿り着いた 本当の居場所 (ホンモノは)
The true place we arrived at (the real deal)
今、最高の夢歌い出した
has now started singing its ultimate dream.
Guys! 他人の人生にちょっかい出す前に
Guys! Before meddling in other people's lives,
Guys! First of all自分の人生を
Guys! First of all, your own life—
相手してやれ 一生懸命
deal with it with all your might!
不・言・実・行!
Actions speak louder than words!
Guys! 千里の道も一歩からさ
Guys! A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step.
Guys! Don’t be shy 万事休す
Guys! Don't be shy, all is lost—
孤独だったとしてもその果てのAnswerを信じろ
even if you were lonely, believe in the answer at the end.
同調圧力なんてクソ喰らえ
To hell with peer pressure!
Go away! 右向け左へ
Go away! Look right, look left!
自己犠牲なんてクソ喰らえ
To hell with self-sacrifice!
Go away! 自分を愛で愛で
Go away! Love yourself, love yourself!
Play with me!!!
愛してやまないモノを Go after! OUTSIDER RODEO
Go after what you love endlessly! OUTSIDER RODEO
Play with me!!!
お前と僕の“マジ”で 一触即発→友情→永遠不滅★
With your and my "sincerity," touch-and-go -> friendship -> eternal!
自分を自分人の好きなように (生きていけ)
Live your life just as you like (live on)!
今、本当にしたいことはなんだ?
What is it you truly want to do right now?
EXPOSE 'Burn out!!!' RAISE A SUILEN
[Title: EXPOSE 'Burn out!!!']
ココロの淵から 舌を舐めずり
Licking my lips from the depths of the heart
暗い呪文並べて Aiming for
lining up dark incantations, aiming for it.
笑顔で凶暴さを Calm down たしなめて
Calming down the ferocity with a smile,
仮面を取り替え引っ換え引っ掛けやってる
swapping out masks over and over.
Show time!
Hi ★ What happened? 常に何かのシンドロームでドッドロ
Hi ★ What happened? Always soaked in some syndrome, muddy.
安心？ (No!) 平常心？ (No!)
At ease? (No!) Peace of mind? (No!)
いつまでやってんの？ おヒマなんですか？
How long are you gonna keep this up? Are you that free?
Listen with attention…
Listen with attention...
Let's ブチ壊して
Let's smash it to pieces!
(Countdown 3,2,1)
(Countdown 3, 2, 1)
Ready go!
Mark my words!
何もかも 今すぐ暴露し出せ (Everybody)
Expose everything right now (Everybody)!
獣みたく叫べよ You can change your world!
Scream like a beast, you can change your world!
僕たちの歌で “Welcome to US”
With our song, "Welcome to US"
Let it go…Let it go…Let it go…
Let it go... Let it go... Let it go...
(Get your gun! Let's shoot! Bang! Bang!)
笑止千万 撃ち砕け!
Crush this ridiculous nonsense!
(Get your gun! Let's shoot! Bang! Bang!)
偽善者たちよ バイバイ
Fake hypocrites, say goodbye.
お口を開けば 噴き出すモヤモヤ
Every time you open your mouth, frustrations spew out,
不平不満 罵詈雑言 etc…
complaints, abuse, profanity, etc...
育てていたんだ Do you know? いつの間にか
cultivating them, do you know? Before you knew it,
花火が踊り出し ハシャゴ
fireworks started dancing wildly, let's party!
Show time!
Hi ★ Are you all right? お得意の言い訳を並べてイイわね？
Hi ★ Are you all right? Lining up your favorite excuses, aren't you?
大事？ (No!) 一大事？ (No!)
Crucial? (No!) Very crucial? (No!)
よく飽きないなあ こっち はもう飽きちゃってんだ
Aren't you tired of it? I'm already so over it.
Listen with attention…
Listen with attention...
前にならえに
Following the crowd,
(Countdown 3,2,1)
(Countdown 3, 2, 1)
ナ・ラ・ウ・ナ！
don't copy them!
Mark my words!
何もかも 今すぐ解き放て (Everybody)
Release everything right now (Everybody)!
獣みたく怖がらずに You can change your world!
Without fear like a beast, you can change your world!
僕たちの歌で “Welcome to US”
With our song, "Welcome to US"
己の意味 示せよ
Prove your existence now,
(I say, You say, We say)
“ココ”で
right here!
(I say, You say, We say)
Listen with attention…
Listen with attention...
快進撃のChance
Chance of a triumphant advance,
(Countdown 3,2,1)
(Countdown 3, 2, 1)
Ready go!
Mark my words!
何もかも 今すぐ暴き出せ (Everybody)
Expose everything right now (Everybody)!
獣みたく正直に You can change your world!
Stay true like a beast, you can change your world!
Mark my words!
何もかも 今すぐ暴露し出せ (Everybody)
Expose everything right now (Everybody)!
獣みたく叫べよ You can change your world!
Scream like a beast, you can change your world!
僕たちの歌で “Welcome to US”
With our song, "Welcome to US"
Let it go…Let it go…Let it go…
Let it go... Let it go... Let it go...
(Get your gun! Let's shoot! Bang! Bang!)
笑止千万 撃ち砕け!
Crush this ridiculous nonsense!
(Get your gun! Let's shoot! Bang! Bang!)
偽善者たちよ バイバイ
Fake hypocrites, say goodbye.
(Don't run away!)
Don't run away!
Mark my words!
Hang in there. It's up to you.
(Don't run away!)
喜びや悲しみ知った頃から
From the days I first knew joy and sorrow,
見上げる空いつでも笑う
the sky I look up at always smiles.
不安も希望に変えてこのまま
Turning anxiety into hope just like this,
きっと願いは今を満たす
surely my wish will fulfill the present.
進み出す また空を指し示す
Advancing, pointing up at the sky once more,
あの日と変わらず青く輝く
shining blue just like that day.
進み出す going slowlyではなく
Moving forward, not going slowly,
時に激しく揺さぶられかけ強引
sometimes shaken fiercely and forcefully.
Sorry! 先に向かうステージ
Sorry! Heading onward to the stage.
いつの時代も解くか? ladies & gentlemen
Decoding any era? Ladies & gentlemen.
絡むブレンド感 音と言葉なら鮮度か
Blending sounds and words with freshness.
始まるさyou know? いくつも苦労話や
It's beginning, you know? Many tales of hardship.
ここで終わるよりは まだ マシ 幸運へ進むぜ lord a mercy
Moving forward to fortune, lord a mercy.
だからツレと結合 仲間とテスト 簡単だろ
Bonding with pals, testing with homies, easy right?
ここぞ上げるベスト ダサめな言葉なら「LET'S GO」
If it's lame words just say "LET'S GO".
半透明で生温い感情 押し流され
Translucent and lukewarm emotions.
フチでまわり 沸々と怒り 果てはひとつ混沌の海
Ending up in a single sea of chaos.
スクランブルするバイナリーをシャッフル 揺るるYes,No
Shuffling scrambling binaries, shaking Yes, No.
フィードバック ループでゴールへGO!
Feedback looping to the goal, GO!
Let it go let it go let it go!
喜びや悲しみ知った頃から
From the days I first knew joy and sorrow,
見上げる空いつでも笑う 生きてゆくだけ
the sky I look up at always smiles.
不安も希望に変えてこのまま
Turning anxiety into hope just like this.
きっと願いは今を満たす 輝く未来へBye-bye!
Surely my wish will fulfill the present.
Don't walk away... Don't walk away...
Don't walk away...
Time to go... Time to go...
Time to you...
PAVOLIA REINE MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
Attention Please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Are you by any chance a MERAKyats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Are you by any chance a MERAKyats who just can't wait for a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Or are you wanting to flex with super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's Membership (that is mine, by the way).
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm here to explain my membership (that's mine, by the way).
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
At The Royaltea, our advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off everytime you're here with us.
which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging by granting you a one of a kind experience with cute emojis.
We also provide utmost care and sense of belonging with a unique experience and cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
At just the right price, you can join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
which also means membership exclusive streams in which we can have various talks, play games together and do other miscellaneous members involvements.
which means exclusive streams for talks, playing games, and other member involvements.
Like what, you might ask...? Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed but it is a part of our character development training
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it's part of our character development training
in which we aim to build a community of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
御伽話は さっき死んだみたい
The fairy tale seems to have died just now.
煉瓦の病棟でうまく歌えなくて
Unable to sing well in the brick ward,
霧に煙る夜浮かべる赤い月
a red moon floats on a night hazy with fog.
ほら見せて私を 目を逸らさないで
Hey, look at me, don't look away.
黒い鉄格子の中で私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born inside a black iron lattice.
悪意の代償を願え 望むがままにお前に
Pray for the compensation of malice, as much as you desire.
さあ与えよう正義を
Now, I shall grant you justice.
壊して 壊される前に
Destroy before you are destroyed.
因果の代償を払い 共に行こう 名前のない怪物
Pay the compensation of karma, let's go together, nameless monster.
耳鳴りがしている 鉄筋網うざくって
My ears are ringing, the barbed wire is so annoying,
思い出せないのあの日の旋律
I can't remember the melody of that day.
雨はまだ止まない 何にも見えないの
The rain still hasn't stopped, I can't see anything.
ほら見て こんなに大きくなったの
Hey look how big it's gotten.
黒い雨降らせこの空 私は望まれないもの
Make black rain fall from this sky, I am unwanted,
ひび割れたノイローゼ
a cracked neurosis.
愛する同罪の傍観者達に さあ今振るえ正義を
To the equally guilty onlookers I love, now shake that justice.
消せない傷を抱きしめて この身体を受け入れ 共に行こう 名前のない怪物
Embracing scars that won't fade, accepting this body, let's go together, nameless monster.
神ハ告ゲル 真ノ世界ヲ...
God proclaims the true world...
大衆娯楽やセンセーショナルで
With mass entertainment and sensationalism,
異論を排して安住の心を
rejecting dissent for peace of mind,
まるで劣化の猿真似みたいだ
it's like a degraded, monkey-see-monkey-do act.
沸き立つ熱気も何処吹く風で
The boiling heat blows wherever it pleases,
最終的には強者の雄叫び
ultimately just the battle cry of the strong.
中身が無いのに醜い代物
An ugly thing devoid of substance,
恥じらう嫉妬もお笑い種です
even shy jealousy is a laughingstock.
腹立つ決起も踊れや踊れ
Even angry uprisings, dance and dance,
曲がったステンレスみたいな
like bent stainless steel,
思い抱いて泣いてしまおうか
shall we hold these thoughts and cry?
忘れないわ 貴方の劣等感も偶然も
I won't forget your inferiority complex or accidents,
カナリア泣いた夜でさえ
even the night the canary wept.
消せる涙 真夏の疾走感で噛らっちゃって
Wiping away tears, devoured by midsummer speed,
石楠花 一輪 捨てちまえなら
if you're going to throw away a single rhododendron,
多大なる迷惑 失礼しました
sorry for the great trouble, excuse me.
今後は暫く大人しくします
I'll be quiet for a while from now on.
それでは別れのお歌をどうぞ
Now then, enjoy the song of farewell.
私を呼んでもそこにはいません
Even if you call me, I won't be there.
狭い大海で弱者を虐げて
Bullying the weak in a narrow ocean,
とても有意義な気持ちでしょうね
it must feel very meaningful, right?
こちらは貴方を許さないようにと
So that I won't forgive you,
ああ
Ah...
疲れた…
I'm tired...
馬鹿だな くららね理想だ
How foolish, what a hazy ideal.
分かっておくれ 泣いてしまった
Please understand, I ended up crying.
忘れないわ 貴方の劣等感も偶然も
I won't forget your inferiority complex or accidents,
カナリア泣いた夜でさえ
even the night the canary wept.
消せる涙 真夏の疾走感で噛らっちゃって
Wiping tears, devoured by midsummer speed,
石楠花 一輪 捨てちまえ
throw away a single rhododendron.
忘れないわ 貴方の劣等感も偶然も
I won't forget your inferiority complex or accidents,
カナリア泣いた夜でさえ
even the night the canary wept.
消せる涙 真夏の疾走感で噛らっちゃって
Wiping tears, devoured by midsummer speed,
石楠花 一輪 捨てちまえなら
if you're going to throw away a single rhododendron,
多大なる迷惑 失礼しました
sorry for the great trouble, excuse me.
今後は暫く大人しくします
I'll be quiet for a while from now on.
それでは別れのお歌をどうぞ
Now then, enjoy the song of farewell.
私を呼んでもそこにはいません
Even if you call me, I won't be there.
狭い大海で弱者を虐げて
Bullying the weak in a narrow ocean,
とても有意義な気持ちでしょうね
it must feel very meaningful, right?
こちらは貴方を許さないようにと
So that I won't forgive you,
匂い立つ世界を震え声を
Shaking voice in a fragrant world,
伏せないで 駆り立てて このからだを受け入れてと もり行こう
don't look down, drive yourself, accept this body, let's go on
I hope you guys are having fun so far!
What do you guys think? What do you guys think about this outfit?
This is the first time you guys are seeing this one, right? The last one, the one before this...
you saw that last time when I was doing the uh... when I was doing the thing.
The thing? But uh, yeah.
This is new, you know?
The other outfit, I'm wearing a, you know, a pair of short pants, and I thought to myself, you know, maybe I'll just get myself, you know, to wear a skirt, a dress.
Look at this, so cute, right?
We have a ribbon on top of my head, which is new.
You know, we have this hairpin, even though we have a ribbon, you0, can't have Reine without the hairpin, I think.
You know, we have this hairpin, even though we have a ribbon, you know, can't have Reine without the hairpin, I think.
And um, we have this tie, so cute! Yeah.
And these shoes, ready to step on things such as, you know, the floor grass, uh, etc.
And these socks, you know, so cute, right? Look at this.
Yeah, hope you guys like it. Hope I surprised you enough with this.
And I'm gonna... I'm just gonna twirl so you guys can see it, you know, I mean you guys could see it before this, but, you know, look closely so you guys can see. I'm gonna twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl...
Yeah!
See, that's what the back part looks like.
But yes, um, welcome to our first talking segment.
What should I talk about? How's the weather today?
How's the weather today? Yeah.
Well, you know what? Uh, I guess we should move to the next song, right?
Hope you guys are staying hydrated
because we still have much more!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no 低音響かせな
Come on, "Say no", now let's bring the bass
なんだか…ってつまらないこともあるでしょう
Don't know what to say, things tend to get boring
ロンリー理論のノート ハンディ真面目脱走
Lonely logic note, handy serious escape
やんないちゃって泥に bad ご法度だろうが
Can't take this anymore, it's bad taboo
溺れて堕ちて そろそろいっか
But drown and drop in mud, it's about time
もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
Let's work harder, let's work harder until I get excited
つながろうひとりよりふたり 増えたら安心 心配ないや
Let's connect, two is better than one / No worries at all
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright let me do it, don't mind
波あり難題 みんなで乗りかかっちゃえば
If we all ride the waves of problems, perhaps it's easy to solve
案外さくっと行ってしまいそう
It turns out smoother than you'd think
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no 低音響かせな
Come on, "Say no", now let's bring the bass
今宵は暗転パーティー
Tonight's a party in the dark
踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness, it's a full house
痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it
ここでバイバイ let go
It's time to say bye-bye, let go
どんな劣等感だって
Any complex,
即興の血小板で
with a style platelet
抑え込んで 突っ込んで 仕舞い込むんでしょう
Hold it, shove it, take it away
Up and down なテンション
Pumped up and down, pretty much stressed out
ねぇまいっちゃってんの相当
Spit it out at once, and give yourself away
ドバッと突き出すのは 本音の独り言
What robots spit out is to the bone
別に興味ない
Not really interested
特に関係ない
Don't really care
塞ぎ込んで 零すポゼッション
Shutting it in, spilling the possession
合図を奏でて PrrPrrPrr
Send signal, prr, prr, prr, prr
ほら集まって夜行だ 鳴いていこうぜ
Let's come together, live the night, we be roaring
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness, it's a full house
痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it
今宵も暗転パーティーだ
Tonight's a party in the dark
どんな時だって きっと
No matter when, surely
速攻の決勝戦まで突っ込んでストレッチしよう
Let's rush straight to the finals and stretch out
Oh yeah!
Up and down なテンション
Up and down tension
目眩いっちゃってんのその下
Dizzy outside
ロボット吐き出すのは 骨の髄まで
What robots spit out is to the bone
別に興味ない
Not really interested
特に関係ない
Don't really care
塞ぎ込んで 零すポゼッション
Shutting it in, spilling the possession
アイスを枯らして
With love stolen
プルプルのーや
Purupuru uya
鳴らして 夜行を
Ring the night train
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
泣いて行こう
Let's go crying
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
泣いて行こう
Let's go crying
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Dance, dance
孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Sanitize loneliness, full house
痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it
ここでバイバイ let go
It's time to say bye-bye, let go
一歩見舞え 押しやれ
Take a step, push it aside
今宵も暗転パーティーだ
Tonight's a party in the dark
またの お越しを きっと
We look forward to serving you again
次回までお元気で
Please take care until next time
ここでバイバイ let go
It's time to say bye-bye, let go
空がどんな高くても
No matter how high the sky is
羽根が千切れ散っても
No matter how shredded your wings are
飛び立つこと恐れずに 焦がせ不死なる絆
Without fearing taking flight, set your immortal bonds ablaze
Fly to the sky… Fire bird!
Fly to the sky... Fire bird!
潰れぬ夢へ燃え上がれ
Blaze a path towards your unending dream!
ついにの夢へ 燃やがれ！
To the ultimate dream... ignite!
空飛ぶカップ パラレル マップ タイム トリック
Flying teacups, parallel maps, time tricks...
きみにだけ教えよう
Let me teach you alone.
消えない烈火 溶けない六花
An unextinguishable fierce fire, an unmelting snowflake,
不死身の橙果
an immortal orange fruit!
きみならわかるはず
If it's you, you should understand.
大人たちは顔うつむけ ビー玉の目曇らせているけれど
The adults hang their heads, their marble eyes clouded over,
ぼくらだけ知っている
but only we know.
信じる力 奇跡起こすこと
The power to believe creates miracles.
たとえ悪魔がきみを拐おこうとしてもきっと！
Even if demons try to kidnap you, surely!
夜空駆け抜ける女神 虹の翼でラリアット
Goddess running through the night sky, rariart on rainbow wings!
この世界がきみを消し去ろうとしても resist!
Even if this world tries to erase you, resist!
ぼくが光追い越してきみを守るよ
I will outrun the light and protect you!
アイリスは神の messenger girl きみを導く虹の usher
Iris on a mission, let me be your guide.
一緒に翔ぼう 時を越えて
Let's fly together across time!
wanna be like...
ikura-man!
大人たちは顔うつむけ ビー玉の目曇らせているけれど
The adults hang their heads, their marble eyes clouded over,
ぼくらだけ知っている
but only we know.
信じる力 奇跡起こすこと
The power to believe creates miracles.
たとえ悪魔がきみを拐おこうとしてもきっと！
Even if demons try to kidnap you, surely!
夜空駆け抜ける女神 虹の翼でラリアット
Goddess running through the night sky, rariart on rainbow wings!
この世界がきみを消し去ろうとしても resist!
Even if this world tries to erase you, resist!
ぼくが光追い越してきみを守るよ
I will outrun the light and protect you!
虹ノ矢ハ折レナイ
The arrow of time!
Through music and rhyme!
次元列車
Track through the dimension,
秘密の結社 呪いの術者
spellcasting connections and secret conventions.
きみとなら怖くない
When you are near, there's no need to fear.
だけど前に前だけにきっと
Call me a cynic approaching the limit,
光はさそうじゅんていよんと
my heart in my lyrics!
大人たちは希望忘れ
While the old lose their way and forget about faith,
氷の中閉じ籠もっている
while the rain turns to ice, their hearts lock like a vice.
だけどぼくらだけ知っている
While we know in our soul the one hope, the one truth,
愛する炎すべて溶かすこと
the fires of love can warm any heart.
たとえ誰かが夢を奪おうとしても上等！
Resist! Your dreams are worth defending.
輝く瞳があればきみは無敵のピラミッド
Fight on, your will is unbending.
最初は上を見ることも
First, let's look above.
それを望むこともまことはがった
That's what I desired, and now I know.
過去の中からの銀河は温かく
The stars in the deep are shining brightly,
その星の輝きに憧れては
such starlight, so dazzling, so regretful!
ただ眩しくって ただ悔しくって
Just dazzling, just frustrating...
だけど今は一言歌おう
but now, let's join as one!
羽ばたこう 頂点の夢と
Fluttering to the peak of our dreams!
夜空駆け抜ける女神 虹の翼でラリアット
Goddess running through the night sky, rariart on rainbow wings!
この世界がきみを消し去ろうとしても resist!
Even if this world tries to erase you, resist!
ぼくが光追い越してきみを守るよ
I will outrun the light and protect you!
再び誓う
Let's swear once more,
頂点への究極のミッション
cresting the ultimate dimensional mission!
ぼくが光追い越してきみを守るよ
I will outrun the light and protect you!
この光るロードを駆け抜けるよ
Seizing the glowing rainbow road!
歌おう新世界を
Let's sing a new world into existence!
invincible rainbow arrow
空とぶカップ パラレルマップ
Flying cups, parallel maps,
タイムトリップ 君にだけ
time trips, only for you—
教えよう
let me teach you.
消えない雷か解けない理力 節目の奇跡君にだけ
Undying thunder, unbreakable power, a turning point's miracle, only for you—
分かるはず
you should understand.
大人たちは顔をうつむけ ビラマロの目曇らせてる
Adults hang their heads down, clouding their eyes with sorrow.
だけど僕らだけ知ってる 信じる力
Yet, only we know the power to believe,
奇跡を起こすこと
to make miracles happen.
たとえ悪魔が君を誘惑しても きっと夜空駆け抜ける女神
Even if demons tempt you, surely the goddess running through the night sky...
虹の翼でリアッと
with rainbow wings, riotto...
この世界が君を消し去ろうとしても レジスト僕が光を追い越して
Even if this world tries to erase you, I will resist, outpacing the light...
君を守るよ
to protect you.
一階の列車 秘密の決者 呪いの呪車 君となら
First-floor train, secret society, cursed carriage—with you,
壊れるくらい 心にそっと触れたアセット
an asset that gently touched the heart until it breaks.
迫るリミット あの瞳に 努力だな
The approaching limit in those eyes—such an effort.
大人たちは希望を忘れ 遠いの中閉じこもってる だけど僕らだけ知ってる
Adults forget hope, shutting themselves away in the distance. Yet, only we know...
愛する炎を
the flame of love,
全て届くこと
reaching everywhere.
たとえ誰かが夢を奪おうとしても ちょっと輝く瞳があれば
Even if someone tries to steal our dreams, if we have shining eyes...
君は無敵のピラミッド
you are an invincible pyramid.
この瞬間が夢を滅ぼそうとしても レボルト僕らの信じる気持ち
Even if this moment tries to destroy dreams, our revolting feelings of belief...
消して負けない 愛の言い訳なんて
will never lose. Excuses of love...
キリストは髪のメセンジャーが 君を導く虹のアッシャー
Christ is a messenger of hair, a rainbow usher guiding you.
一緒に共時を越えて 笑い合おう
Let's cross synchronization together and smile at each other.
大人たちは顔をうつむけ ビラマロの目曇らせてる
Adults hang their heads down, clouding their eyes.
だけど僕らだけ知ってる 信じる力
Yet, only we know the power to believe,
奇跡を起こすこと
to make miracles happen.
たとえ悪魔が君を誘惑しても きっと夜空駆け抜ける女神
Even if demons tempt you, surely the goddess running through the night sky...
虹の翼でリアッと
with rainbow wings, riotto...
この世界が君を消し去ろうとしても レジスト僕が光を追い越して
Even if this world tries to erase you, I will resist, outpacing the light...
君を守るよ
to protect you.
虹の矢折れない 2人の矢折れない
Rainbow arrows won't break, our two arrows won't break.
Hi! Hi guys, doing now?
Hi! Hi, guys, how're you doing?
Are you guys doing okay?
Stay hydrated.
Thank you so much for, uh, Infightbird, I asked some help from my talented, talented, talented friends.
Thank you so much for, uh, In-Fitbird. I asked for some help from my talented, talented, talented friends.
Thank you so much to Kiara, Ollie, Muna, and Kobo for helping me with the choruses as well as the solo parts.
We've sang so much songs today, so many songs, but, well,
We've sung so many songs today, so many songs, but, well,
there's still, there's still some some things, you know, it's not over yet, obviously.
there's still, there's still some things, you know, it's not over yet, obviously.
Well, uh, I don't know, what do you guys think about this?
What time do you think it is?
Nice.
Well, I heard you loud and clear even though it's in your heart.
Well, I heard you loud and clear,even though it's in your heart.
The uh, it's time for the long-awaited segment of this live I've been dying to like
It's time for the long-awaited segmentof this live I've been dying to...
I've been dying to like, e, just like vomit everything out of my mouth.
I've been dying to, you know,just vomit everything out of my mouth.
It is time for some Instagram marketing of, drumroll please!
It is time for some Instagram marketingof... drumroll please!
in your heart, drumroll.
You guys did right.
You guessed right!
It is time for birthday goods announcement!
It is time for the birthday goods announcement!
Look at that beautiful, beautiful, beautiful illustration.
Look at that beautiful,beautiful, beautiful illustration.
We have multiple items today.
We have the spicy 1000 ReineMat and the GWS plus.
We have the "SPY-C1000 ReineMat"and the "GWS+".
Very nice, right? I uh, you know, origin um that came from my brain. I'm sure you guys love the name.
Very nice, right? That name just camefrom my brain. I'm sure you guys love it.
Uh yes, it's a big, big, big, big rubber mat.
Yes, it's a big, big, big,big rubber mat!
And, you know, look at this. It's a, yeah, super big size.
And look at this, it's asuper big size.
So maybe if you guys are used to, uh, smaller rubber mats, well this one's big, so, you know, big is good, I guess.
If you guys are used to smaller rubber mats,well, this one's big, so big is good, I guess!
Uh, yeah, because it's size is 60 by 90.
Yeah, because its size is60 by 90 centimeters!
And look at that beautiful art from Pochi Mama. Look at that, my super neat room, no mess, so nice, right?
And look at that beautiful art from Pochi Mama!My super neat room, no mess, so nice, right?
Yeah, what are you waiting for? Don't you want your own Reine room in your room?
Yeah, what are you waiting for?Don't you want a Reine room in your room?
Then you know what to do.
Spicy, so so so so spicy, rainy spicy room in your spicy room.
Spicy, so, so, so spicy!A rainy spicy room in your spicy room.
And the second one, we also have a drinking mug, extra extra extra large size.
And second, we also have a drinking mug,extra, extra, extra large size!
That's why, you know, uh today the theme is kind of big, you know, we have the small Reine, but uh our merch is big.
That's why today's theme is kind of big.We have the small Reine, but our merch is big!
Our drinking mug is actually extra large size with approximately 1L volume.
Our drinking mug is extra large,with approximately 1 liter of volume!
So all of you like thirsty people, don't worry, you will never get thirsty as long as you watch Reine, well you drinking from this mug, okay?
So all you thirsty people, don't worry,you'll never get thirsty using this mug.
Look at that beautiful, beautiful, beautiful art. Look at that, so cute. You would want one.
Look at that beautiful, beautiful art!So cute, you'll want one.
Or two, or three, you know. It's all right. Any amount is okay.
Or two, or three, you know.It's all right, any amount is okay!
And yeah, if you buy the merch as a set, you will get a bonus postcard.
And if you buy the merch as a set,you will get a bonus postcard!
Ta-da! Which is very very very similar to the rubber mat,
Ta-da! Which is very, very similarto the rubber mat,
except has a different expression. Look at that, so spicy, what a spicy expression.
except it has a different expression.Look at that, what a spicy expression!
And it comes with a handwritten autograph. Can you imagine it? Handwritten autograph in my Reine merch?
And it comes with a handwritten autograph!Can you imagine? A handwritten autograph in my merch!
Tunggu apa lagi, mudah sekali! So easy, guys. What are you waiting for?
Tunggu apa lagi, mudah sekali!So easy, guys, what are you waiting for?
You know, I don't know if goods sales is open yet, but what are you waiting for? If it's not open, you know, it's just like be on standby, you know what to do.
I don't know if merch sales are open yet,but if not, just be on standby, you know what to do!
And yeah, so on the corner of the postcard, you know, there will be like, uh, nice, uh nice signature, so cute Reine, you know. You want your own, uh, authentic Reine signature, right? Yes, autograph, autograph, autograph.
On the corner of the postcard, there's a nicesignature! You want your own authentic signature, right?
Yes, so that is it, you know, after seeing this, you know, if you don't think
So after seeing this, if you don't think...
If you don't think, oh it's so cute, it's so spicy, I want to buy it, then you will think that soon.
"Oh, it's so cute, it's so spicy, I want to buy it!"You'll be thinking that soon.
So, you know, just like be on standby and buy it as soon as as it's available. Okay, okay, okay, okay, yay!
So just be on standby and buy itas soon as it's available, okay? Yay!
Oh yes, thank you so much, uh, Kawanu for making this happen.
Oh yes, thank you so much,Kawanu, for making this happen.
This is not the end.
After this, there will be one more song.
Well, what song? Is it going to be another one of those what are those Well, you know, another cover song?
Well, what song? Is it going to beanother one of those cover songs?
No.
Reine finally singing her original song! Oh my god, really?
Reine is finally singing her original song!Oh my god, really?
And not just just an original song, I'm going to be singing my new original song, which will be available
And not just an original song,my new original song,
starting September 10 000000 at your local time.
which will be available starting September 10that 00:00 local time!
So, get ready for that. Have you guys um Have you guys are ready?
So get ready for that!Have you guys...
Yes! It's an English song, is-
is the very, very, very first time I'm singing an English song,
and it's gonna be...
the first time you guys will be hearing this song for the first time here.
Okay?
Okay, what are you waiting for?
So easy, mudah sekali, just sit back and listen, and sing along maybe, and dance along,
So easy, very easy, just sit back and listen, and sing along maybe, and dance along,
Let's go!
Are you guys excited?
Get ready for... Illusion Night.
Kiss me! Keep those lips from wandering off,
tell me every sweet and tender thought!
Give me all you have to give and more...
fantasies where futures are born!
Can you feel the beat? The rhythm, the tune...
your heart and mine - the countdown!
If you feel something coming to you, believe it and scream it aloud!
I don't think I'll miss you anymore, like I did the day you left.
There's so many just like you, I could use instead!
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end.
This city will swallow the pain...
tomorrow's another today...
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
Spend our moment dancing in the moonlight!
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body, keep your eyes on me!
Take me somewhere, deep into the night...
touch me - here, there, anywhere you like!
Trust me! Won't you let me look inside?
Fantasies and futures collide...
it's just the two of us beneath the starry sky...
If the only way to keep on living is "keep on living strong,"
then you can keep the kindness,
'cause I'm moving on!
No need to say "goodbye" to me - I'm already gone!
Just wipe all your tears away,
and know we'll start over someday...
All your heart, your soul, your body...
you belong to one and only!
Unconditionally yearning, knowing no one else will do...
can you feel the bond between us grow tight? We're closer than we've ever been!
Follow me! Match your rhythm to mine,
and let it all out from within!
I don't think I'll miss you any more than I did the day you left...
I won't say "I love you."
I know I'll take it back!
I'm used to this. I'm not the same old loser that burned bright and quick,
when candles and wind could never last!
A city that's living in fast-forward's
the perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance!
There's nothing here to stop us – when in Rome, romance!
And I won't let you leave me alone without a dance!
I don't wanna 'hear a goodbye...
don't break the illusion tonight...
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
Spend forever living 'til the sunrise!
Feel that look, even with the lights off, dance until we drop!
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
Spend forever living 'til the sunrise!
Feel that look, even with the lights off, dance until we drop!
kiss me ! keep those lips from wandering off
Kiss me! Keep those lips from wandering off,
tell me every sweet and tender thought !
Tell me every sweet and tender thought!
give me all you have to give and more . . .
Give me all you have to give and more...
fantasy ’s where futures are born !
Fantasy's where futures are born!
can you feel the beat ? the rhythm , the tune . . .
Can you feel the beat? The rhythm, the tune...
your heart and mine – the countdown . . .
Your heart and mine – the countdown...
if you feel something coming to you ,
If you feel something coming to you,
believe it and scream it aloud !
Believe it and scream it aloud!
i don’t think “ i ’ ll miss you . . . ” anymore , like i did the day you left .
I don't think "I'll miss you..." anymore, like I did the day you left.
there ’s so many just like you , i could use instead !
There's so many just like you, I could use instead!
’ cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end .
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end.
this city will swallow the pain . . .
This city will swallow the pain...
tomorrow ’s another today . . .
Tomorrow's another today...
curtain call ’s at dawn , darling ! showtime !
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
spend our moment dancing in the moonlight !
Spend our moment dancing in the moonlight!
’ til your gaze starts swaying with my body . . .
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body...
keep your eyes on me !
Keep your eyes on me!
take me somewhere , deep into the night . . .
Take me somewhere, deep into the night...
touch me – here , there , anywhere you like !
Touch me – here, there, anywhere you like!
trust me ! won’t you let me look inside ?
Trust me! Won't you let me look inside?
fantasies and futures collide …
Fantasies and futures collide...
it ’s just the two of us beneath the starry sky . . .
It's just the two of us beneath the starry sky...
if the only way to keep on living is “ keep on living strong ! ”
If the only way to keep on living is "Keep on living strong!"
then , you can keep the kindness , ’ cause i ’m moving on !
Then, you can keep the kindness, 'cause I'm moving on!
no need to say “ goodbye ” to me – i ’m already gone !
No need to say "goodbye" to me – I'm already gone!
just wipe all your tears away
and know we ’ll start over someday . . .
And know we'll start over someday...
all your heart , your soul , your body …
All your heart, your soul, your body...
you belong to one and only !
You belong to one and only!
unconditionally yearning ,
Unconditionally yearning,
knowing no one else will do . . .
Knowing no one else will do...
can you feel the bond between us grow tight ?
Can you feel the bond between us grow tight?
we ’re closer than we ’ve ever been !
We're closer than we've ever been!
follow me ! match your rhythm to mine ,
Follow me! Match your rhythm to mine,
and let it all out from with in !
And let it all out from within!
i don’t think i miss you any more than i did the day you left . . .
I don't think I miss you any more than I did the day you left...
i won’t say “ i love you . ” i know i ’ll take it back !
I won't say "I love you." I know I'll take it back!
i ’m used to this . i ’m not the same old loser that
I'm used to this. I'm not the same old loser that
burned bright and quick , when candles and wind could never last !
Burned bright and quick, when candles and wind could never last!
a city that ’s living in fast-forward ’s
A city that's living in fast-forward's
the perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance !
The perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance!
there ’s nothing here to stop us – when in rome , romance !
There's nothing here to stop us – when in Rome, romance!
and , i won’t let you leave me alone without a dance !
And, I won't let you leave me alone without a dance!
i don’t wanna ’ hear a goodbye . . .
I don't wanna hear a goodbye...
don’t break the illusion tonight . . .
Don't break the illusion tonight...
curtain call ’s at dawn , darling ! showtime !
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
spend forever living ’ til the sunrise !
Spend forever living 'til the sunrise!
feel that look , even with the lights off . . .
Feel that look, even with the lights off...
dance until we drop !
Dance until we drop!
kiss me ! keep those lips from wandering off
Kiss me! Keep those lips from wandering off,
tell me every sweet and tender thought !
Tell me every sweet and tender thought!
give me all you have to give and more . . .
Give me all you have to give and more...
fantasy ’s where futures are born !
Fantasy's where futures are born!
can you feel the beat ? the rhythm , the tune . . .
Can you feel the beat? The rhythm, the tune...
your heart and mine – the countdown . . .
Your heart and mine – the countdown...
if you feel something coming to you ,
If you feel something coming to you,
believe it and scream it aloud !
Believe it and scream it aloud!
i don’t think “ i ’ ll miss you . . . ” anymore , like i did the day you left .
I don't think "I'll miss you..." anymore, like I did the day you left.
there ’s so many just like you , i could use instead !
There's so many just like you, I could use instead!
’ cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end .
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end.
this city will swallow the pain . . .
This city will swallow the pain...
tomorrow ’s another today . . .
Tomorrow's another today...
curtain call ’s at dawn , darling ! showtime !
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
spend our moment dancing in the moonlight !
Spend our moment dancing in the moonlight!
’ til your gaze starts swaying with my body . . .
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body...
keep your eyes on me !
Keep your eyes on me!
take me somewhere , deep into the night . . .
Take me somewhere, deep into the night...
touch me – here , there , anywhere you like !
Touch me – here, there, anywhere you like!
trust me ! won’t you let me look inside ?
Trust me! Won't you let me look inside?
fantasies and futures collide …
Fantasies and futures collide...
it ’s just the two of us beneath the starry sky . . .
It's just the two of us beneath the starry sky...
if the only way to keep on living is “ keep on living strong ! ”
If the only way to keep on living is "Keep on living strong!"
then , you can keep the kindness , ’ cause i ’m moving on !
Then, you can keep the kindness, 'cause I'm moving on!
no need to say “ goodbye ” to me – i ’m already gone !
No need to say "goodbye" to me – I'm already gone!
just wipe all your tears away
and know we ’ll start over someday . . .
And know we'll start over someday...
all your heart , your soul , your body …
All your heart, your soul, your body...
you belong to one and only !
You belong to one and only!
unconditionally yearning ,
Unconditionally yearning,
knowing no one else will do . . .
Knowing no one else will do...
can you feel the bond between us grow tight ?
Can you feel the bond between us grow tight?
we ’re closer than we ’ve ever been !
We're closer than we've ever been!
follow me ! match your rhythm to mine ,
Follow me! Match your rhythm to mine,
and let it all out from with in !
And let it all out from within!
i don’t think i miss you any more than i did the day you left . . .
I don't think I miss you any more than I did the day you left...
i won’t say “ i love you . ” i know i ’ll take it back !
I won't say "I love you." I know I'll take it back!
i ’m used to this . i ’m not the same old loser that
I'm used to this. I'm not the same old loser that
burned bright and quick , when candles and wind could never last !
Burned bright and quick, when candles and wind could never last!
a city that ’s living in fast-forward ’s
A city that's living in fast-forward's
the perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance !
The perfect place for lovers like us to take a chance!
there ’s nothing here to stop us – when in rome , romance !
There's nothing here to stop us – when in Rome, romance!
and , i won’t let you leave me alone without a dance !
And, I won't let you leave me alone without a dance!
i don’t wanna ’ hear a goodbye . . .
I don't wanna hear a goodbye...
don’t break the illusion tonight . . .
Don't break the illusion tonight...
curtain call ’s at dawn , darling ! showtime !
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!